Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 1976 Campaign
  - Brown, Edmund Gerald, 1976
    - Campaign literature, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Byrd, Robert, 1976
    - Pamphlet, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Carter, Jimmy Earl, 1976
    - Necklace with a metal peanut, 1976 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-JEC1976-001)
    - Button with printed photograph of Carter and Mondale with text: Carter-Mondale in '76, 1976 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-JEC1976-002)
    - Bumper sticker: Carter '76, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Inauguration guide, materials, 1977 (Box 16)
    - Ephemera, pamphlets, North Carolina campaign, 1976 (Box 16)
    - T-shirt: Not Just Peanuts, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1976
    - Bumper sticker: President Ford, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Stickers: Ford/Dole, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Bumper stickers: Ford/Dole, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Convention pamphlets, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Newspaper advertisement: Anti-Carter caricature, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Harris, Fred, 1976
    - Pamphlet, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Jackson, Henry, 1976
    - Pamphlet, campaign literature, clipping, 1976 (Box 16)
  - MacBride, Roger, 1976
    - Libertarian National Convention pamphlet, doorknob pamphlet, ephemera, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Maddox, Lester, 1976
    - Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Maddox, 1976 (Box 16)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1976
    - Bumper sticker: McCarthy '76, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Campaign literature, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Reagan, Ronald Wilson, 1976
    - Postcard, pamphlet, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Sanford, James Terry, 1976
    - Bumper sticker: Terry Sanford for President, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Shapp, Milton, 1976
    - Pamphlet, campaign literature, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Shriver, Sargent, 1976
    - Postcards, campaign literature, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Udall, Morris King, 1976
    - Button with text: Udall, 1976 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-MKU1976-001)
    - Bumper sticker: Udall for President, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Campaign literature, pamphlet, 1976 (Box 16)
- 1980 Campaign
  - Anderson, John, 1980
    - Bumper stickers: Anderson for President, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Anderson Lucey, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Campaign literature, clippings, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Bush, George H.W., 1980
    - Bumper stickers: George Bush for President, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Carter, Jimmy Earl, 1980
    - Button with text: Re-elect Carter Mondale, 1980 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-JEC1980-001)
    - Pamphlets, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Billy Beer, 1980 (Box 18, Item RL-00580-JEC1980-002)
  - Kennedy, Ted, 1980
    - Pamphlet, campaign literature, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Kennedy '80, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Reagan, Ronald Wilson, 1980
    - Bumper sticker: Students for Reagan, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper stickers: Reagan, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper stickers: Reagan and Bush, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper stickers: Reagan Bush, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: I'm from Durham and I'm for Reagan, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets, flyers, mass mailings, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Pin with red and blue border and printed photographs of Reagan and Bush with text: Reagan-Bush in '80, Let's Make America Great Again, 1980 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-RWR1980-001)
- 1984 Campaign
  - Glenn, John, 1984
    - Campaign literature: Answers the Black Community's Questions, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Hart, Gary, 1984
    - Campaign literature, mass mailings, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1984
    - Campaign literature, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Sticker: Now is the Time: Coalition, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Poster: Jesse Jackson portrait, 1984 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1984
    - Button with text: Vote Nov. 6, 1984 Orange County, NC Mondale Ferraro (Box 8, Item RL-00580-WFM1984-001)
    - Bumper sticker: Mondale/Ferraro, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Mondale/Ferraro, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Mondale, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets, poster, Independents for Mondale literature, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Stickers: Mondale/Ferraro, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Poster: Mondale, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Poster: Ferraro as Lady Liberty, 1984 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald Wilson, 1984
    - Plexidisc for "Stand Up and Cheer for Ronald Reagan", 1984 (Box 1)
    - Button with text: Reagan Bush '84, 1984 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RWR1984-001)
      RL-00580-RWR1984-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002
    - Button with text: Reagan Bush '84, 1984 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RWR1984-002)
      RL-00580-RWR1984-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001
    - Button with text: Reagan Bush '84, 1984 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RWR1984-003)
    - Button with text: Reagan Bush '84, 1984 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RWR1984-004)
    - Bumper sticker: Reagan, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Reagan-Bush '84, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Decal: Americans to Re-elect President Reagan, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets, literature, postcards, Newsweek, sheet music "Stand Up and Cheer for Ronald Reagan", 1984 (Box 16)
- 1988 Campaign
  - Bush, George Herbert Walker, 1988
    - Button with text: George Bush 88, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-001)
    - Button with drawings of George Washington and George Bush and text: Bicentennial Inauguration 1789 1989 George to George 200 Years, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-002)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 003, 4
    - Button with drawings of George Washington and George Bush and text: Bicentennial Inauguration 1789 1989 George to George 200 Years, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-003)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 4
    - Button with drawings of George Washington and George Bush and text: Bicentennial Inauguration 1789 1989 George to George 200 Years, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-004)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3
    - Button with printed photographs of Bush and Quayle and text: 51st American Presidential Inauguration Jan 20, 1989, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-005)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 7
    - Button with printed photographs of Bush and Quayle and text: 51st American Presidential Inauguration Jan 20, 1990, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-006)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 7
    - Button with printed photographs of Bush and Quayle and text: 51st American Presidential Inauguration Jan 20, 1991, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GHB1988-007)
      RL-00580-GHB1988-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 6
  - Dukakis, Michael, 1988
    - Button with text: Noriega/Bush '88 A Crack Team!, 1988 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-MSD1988-001)
  - Robinson, Pat, 1988
    - Mass mailings, 1986 (Box 16)
- 1992 Campaign
  - Clinton, William Jefferson, 1992
    - Bumper sticker: Bill Clinton for President, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Clinton Gore, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlet, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Pin, silver saxophone, 1992 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-WJC1992-001)
- 1996 Campaign
  - Clinton, William Jefferson, 1996
    - Button with text: Clinton Gore 96, 1996 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-WJC1996-001)
    - Button with text: Latino/Latina Vote in 96 Democratic National Committee, 1996 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-WJC1996-002)
    - Bumper sticker: Clinton Gore '96, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Perot, Henry Ross, 1996
    - Button blue, with text: Vote Your Conscience, Perot for President '96 (214) GO-PEROT, 1996 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-RXP1996-001)
- 2000 Campaign
  - Bush, George W., 2000
    - Button with printed photograph of Bush and text: George Bush 2000 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB2000-001)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and text: Bush for President in 2000 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB2000-002)
  - Gore, Albert Arnold, 2000
    - Button with printed color photograph of Gore and text: Gore for President in 2000 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-AAG2000-001)
    - Button with text (Hebrew): Gore Lieberman 2000 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-AAG2000-002)
    - Button with text: Gore Lieberman 2000 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-AAG2000-003)
    - Bumper sticker: Gore Lieberman 2000 (Box 16)
- 2004 Campaign
  - Bush, George W., 2004
    - Button with text: Bush Cheney 2004 Yes, America Can! (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-001)
    - Button with horse and text: It's the Cowboy Way 2004 Bush (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-002)
    - Button with text: George Bush Jr. Richard Cheney W 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-003)
    - Button with printed color photograph of waving Bush and Cheney and text: Renewing America's Purpose Bush Cheney, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-004)
    - Button with text: W 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-005)
    - Button with text: Bush Cheney 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-006)
    - Button with printed color photograph of George and Laura Bush and text: Homeland Heroes, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-007)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and text: George W. Bush President 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-008)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Republican National Convention and text: Minnesotans for Bush Cheney, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-009)
    - Button with elephant and text: Republican National Convention 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-010)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and text: Continuing Excellent Protecting our Future; Connecticut for Bush 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-011)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and Cheney and text: Re-Elect Bush Cheney 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-012)
    - Button with printed color photographs of Bush and Cheney and text: Re-Elect George W. Bush Dick Cheney 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-013)
    - Button with printed color photographs of Bush and Cheney and text: For America George Bush and Dick Cheney, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-014)
    - Button with printed color photographs of Bush and Cheney and text: Protecting America Bush Cheney 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-015)
    - Button with printed color photograph of the Statue of Liberty and text: Republican National Convention, New York, New York Aug. 30-Sept. 2, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-016)
    - Pin with printed color photograph of Bush and Cheney and text: Bush Cheney 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-017)
    - Pin with printed color photograph of Bush and text: Bush 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-GWB2004-018)
  - Dean, Howard Brush, 2004
    - Button with printed color photograph of woman and laptop with text: Geeks for Dean, 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-HBD2004-001)
    - Button with text: Howard Dean for America www.deanforamerica.com, 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-HBD2004-002)
  - Kerry, John, 2004
    - Pin with text: John Kerry President, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-001)
    - Pin with text: Kerry Edwards A Stronger America 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-002)
    - Pin with text: Kerry Edwards A Stronger America, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-003)
    - Pin with text: Kerry 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-004)
    - Button with text: Kerry Edwards A Stronger America, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-005)
      RL-00580-JOK2004-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 7
    - Button with text: Kerry Edwards A Stronger America, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-006)
      RL-00580-JOK2004-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 7
    - Button with text: Kerry Edwards A Stronger America, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-007)
      RL-00580-JOK2004-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 6
    - Button with printed photograph of New York Post and text: Kerry's Choice: Dem picks Gephardt as VP candidate, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-008)
    - Button with printed photographs of Kerry and Edwards with text: For a Stronger America 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-009)
    - Button with printed photographs of Kerry and Edwards with text: The Right Choice for America 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-010)
    - Button with printed photographs of Kerry and Edwards with text: Kerry Edwards 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-011)
    - Button with printed photograph of Kerry in Boston Harbor with text: Welcome to the Democratic National Convention Boston Mass July 26-29 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-012)
    - Button with printed photograph of Kerry and Edwards riding a donkey and text: Victory, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-013)
    - Button with printed photographs of Bush and Cheney crossed out with text: Weapons of Mass Deception, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-014)
    - Button with printed photograph of Bush in a light bulb with text: 1000 Points of Light, 1 Dim Bulb, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-015)
    - Button with printed photograph of Boston skyline and text: 2004 Democratic National Convention Boston, Massachusetts July 26-July 29 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-016)
    - Button with printed photographs of Kerry and Edwards with text: Vote for the Best Democrats 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-017)
    - Button with printed photographs of Ted Kennedy and Kerry with text: Boston's Favorite Sons, 2004 (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-018)
    - Button with text: 2004 Kerry Edwards President Vice President www.johnkerry.com (Box 9, Item RL-00580-JOK2004-019)
  - Nader, Ralph, 2004
    - Button with text: Nader for President 2004 votenader.org (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RXN2004-001)
      RL-00580-RXN2004-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002
    - Button with text: Nader for President 2004 votenader.org (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RXN2004-002)
      RL-00580-RXN2004-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001
- 2008 Campaign
  - McCain, John, 2008
    - Anti-Obama literature, 2008 (Box 16)
    - Campaign literature, 2008 (Box 16)
  - Obama, Barack Hussein, 2008
    - Button with text: Obama Pride LGBT for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-001)
    - Button with text (Hebrew): Obama Biden, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-002)
    - Button with text: Jewish Americans for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-003)
    - Button with text: Veterans and Military Families for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-004)
    - Button with text: Estamos Unidos Latinos for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-005)
    - Button with text: Nurses for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-006)
    - Button with text: Estamos Unidos Hispanics for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-007)
    - Button with text: Environmentalists for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-008)
    - Button with text: Women for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-009)
    - Button with text: Women for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-010)
    - Button with text: Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-011)
    - Button with text: African Americans for Obama, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-012)
    - Button with text: Fired Up Ready to Go!, 2008 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO2008-013)
    - Dark blue pin, words: We For She, 2008 (Box 16)
    - Inauguration ephemera, 2008 (Box 16)
- 2012 Campaign
  - Obama, Barack Hussein, 2012
    - Button with printed photograph of Bo the Dog and text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-001)
    - Button with text: I like Obamacare, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-002)
    - Button with text: I like Obamacare, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-003)
    - Button (magnet) with text: Artists for Obama 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-004)
    - Button with text: O 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-005)
    - Button with text: O 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-006)
    - Button with text: O 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-007)
    - Button with printed photograph of Michelle Obama and text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-008)
    - Button with text: Forward., 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-009)
    - Button with text: Obama 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-010)
    - Button with text: Vote Obama in 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-011)
    - Pin shaped like Connecticut with text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-012)
    - Button with printed photograph of Obama and his family and text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-013)
    - Pin with text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-014)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Obama and text: 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-015)
    - Button with text: 50 Happy Birthday, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-016)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Obama and text: Vote Obama 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-017)
    - Button with drawing of Obama and text: Obama 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-018)
    - Pin with text: Greater Together Obama 2012 (Eddie Borgo Runway to Win) (Box 10, Item RL-00580-BHO2012-019)
  - Romney, Willard Mitt, 2012
    - Button with text: Juntos con Romney, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-001)
    - Button with text: California Delegation VIP Republican National Convention Aug. 27-Aug. 30 2012 Tampa FL (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-002)
    - Pin with text: Romney Ryan, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-003)
    - Button with text: Built by US, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-004)
    - Cufflinks (2) with text: Mitt, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-005)
    - Button with text: Young Americans for Romney, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-006)
    - Button with text: Romney Believe in America, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-007)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Paul Ryan, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-008)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Ann and Mitt Romney, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-009)
    - Button with text: No Money No Jobs No Hope Nobama, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-010)
    - Button with eagle and text: Romney 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-011)
    - Button with text: Women for Mitt, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-012)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Ryan and Romney with text: Romney Ryan, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-013)
    - Button with text: Romney Believe in America, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-014)
    - Pin with text: R 2, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-015)
      RL-00580-WMR2012-015 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0016
    - Pin with text: R 2, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-016)
      RL-00580-WMR2012-016 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015
    - Pin with text: R, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-017)
    - Pin with text: Romney Ryan, 2012 (Box 10, Item RL-00580-WMR2012-018)
- 2016 Campaign
  - Bush, John Ellis, 2016
    - Bumper sticker: Don't Blame Me I Was for Jeb!, 2016 (Box 16)
  - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 2016
    - Button with printed photograph of Clinton and text: June 7, 2016 History made. (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-001)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Hillary and Bill Clinton and text: 1971 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Hillary and Bill Clinton with text: 1983 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-003)
    - Button with printed photograph of Hillary speaking and text: 1984 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-004)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Hillary speaking and text: 1995 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-005)
    - Button with printed photograph of Hillary and text: 2006 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-006)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Hillary as Secretary of State and text: 2010 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-007)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Hillary and Bill Clinton with their baby granddaughter and text: 2014 Hillary for America, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-008)
    - Button with text: #HillYes, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-009)
    - Button with text: #HillYes, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-010)
    - Button with text: I'm with her, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-011)
    - Button with text: Women for H, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-012)
    - Button with text: Latinos for H, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-013)
    - Button with text: Latinos for H, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-014)
    - Woman Card, 2016 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: H->, 2016 (Box 16)
    - Hillary Nutcracker, 2016 (Box 18, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-015)
    - Pin blue with H arrow, words: Clinton Kaine, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-016)
    - Purple pin with H arrow, words: Hillary Is Just My Type, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-017)
    - Turquoise pin with H arrow, words: Hillary Is Just My Type, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-018)
    - Orange pin with H arrow, words: Hillary Is Just My Type, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-019)
    - Red pin, words: Deal Us In, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-020)
    - Light blue pin, words: Votes For Her, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-021)
    - Dark blue pin, words: Fighting For Me Since '73, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-022)
    - Light blue pin, words: Hill&Me, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-023)
    - Dark blue pin, words: We For She, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-024)
    - Pin with woman and American flag, words: Hillary Clinton For President 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-025)
    - Light blue pin, words: She believes in science, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-026)
    - Dark blue pin, words: She does her homework, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-027)
    - Red pin, words: She uses big words, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-028)
    - Green pin with wind turbine, words: We Need To Get Back Into the Future Business, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-029)
    - Red pin with justice balance, words: People Are Crying Out For Criminal Justice Reform, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-030)
    - Blue pin with book and scissors, words: Let's Make Debt-Free College Available to Everyone, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-031)
    - Pin with words: Kennedy, Johnson, Carter, Clinton, Obama, Clinton, Sounds good., 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-032)
    - Pin photograph of Eleanor Roosevelt, black and white, words: Who Says A First Lady Can't Become a Great Leader?, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-033)
    - Red pin, words: It's About Damn Time., 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-034)
    - Pin, word: Her., 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-035)
    - Pin, words: South Korea has one, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-036)
    - Pin, words: The UK has one, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-037)
    - Pin, words: Liberia has one, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-038)
    - Pin, words: Germany has one, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-039)
    - Pin with preach emoji hands, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-040)
    - Pin with words: OH-> yes, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-041)
    - Pin, words: Vote Rodham 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-042)
    - Pin with pigeon, colored, words: Clean Energy Clinton 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-043)
    - Pin, words: Still Love Bernie (blue) Voting For Hillary (red), 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-044)
    - Pin with cartoon of Clinton's face, rainbow hair, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-045)
    - Pin, word: Hillinfrastructure, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-046)
    - Pin, words: Hillimmigration reform, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-047)
    - Pin, word: Hilleducation, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-048)
    - Pin over faded picture, words: Democratic Hillary Rodham Clinton, Democratic, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-049)
    - Pin over faded picture, words: President of Vote, Presidente de los Vote, Hillary, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-050)
    - Pin over faded picture green handle, words: Hillary Clinton, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-051)